http://www.pglrw.org/index.php/about/terms-conditions

Email
This and the following pages contain information about the Provincial Grand Lodge of Renfrewshire West (hereinafter referred to as the ‘Lodge’) copyright and links to external Websites. They also contain an important liability disclaimer.
Copyright
The information contained on this Website is the copyright © property of the Lodge (unless stated otherwise) and is protected by international copyright laws.
The Lodge Website is provided for personal, private and non-commercial use only. No user or recipient has any right to modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, exchange or sell any information, material, software, images, graphics or source code obtained from the Lodge Website.
No part of the Lodge Website may be reproduced in any form whether electronically or otherwise (other than temporarily in the course of using the Website) without the express prior written consent of the Lodge.
Links to External Web Sites
The Lodge has included, or may include, links to third party Internet Web sites controlled and maintained by others. When accessing these links the user leaves the Lodge Website. These links are included solely for the convenience of users and their presence does not constitute any endorsement by the Lodge of the Websites linked or referred to nor does the Lodge have any control over, or responsibility for, the content of any such Websites.
Liability Disclaimer
The Lodge Website is produced and made available in absolute good faith. For the avoidance of any doubt, neither the Lodge nor any of its Trustees, Office-bearers or members give or make any representations or warranties of any kind, whether express, actual or implied, in relation to all or any part of the Lodge Website or any contents thereof or any Website or Websites to which the Lodge Website is linked. All warranties and representations of every kind and howsoever arising are hereby absolutely and expressly excluded to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Liability for material reproduced on the Lodge Website remains with the author(s) and/or originator(s) of the material concerned and not with the Lodge. Responsibility for errors and/or omissions in all material remains with the author(s) and/or originator(s) and not the Lodge.
The content of the Lodge Website does not constitute the dispensation or giving of any kind of advice, recommendations or guidance by or on behalf of the Lodge and must not be relied upon in making, or refraining from making, any decision.
There is no guarantee that the Website will be free of infection whether by viruses or from any other cause or source which may be harmful or destructive. All parties use the Lodge Website entirely at their own risk and without recourse to the Lodge, its Office-bearers, Trustees and members or any of them.
To the fullest extent permitted by law, the Lodge and, separately, its Trustees, Office-bearers and members, all jointly and severally, hereby disclaim all liability (howsoever arising) in connection with any loss or damage, arising out of or in connection with any use of, or inability to use, all or any part of the Lodge Website or any site to which the Lodge Website is linked or any action taken (or not taken) as a result of access to the use of any of these.
Editorial Control
The Lodge can exercise editorial control only over material commissioned and/or produced by it. The Lodge cannot, under any circumstances, change, add to, or subtract from, any material previously produced by others, that is prior to reproduction by the Lodge. Errors and omissions in such previously reproduced material are the responsibility of the original author or commissioning body and not the Lodge. Errors and omissions in material reproduced on the Lodge Website which do not occur in the original material should be brought to the attention of the Web Master. If correction is required, the full text of the original material, author, source, dates and place(s) of primary publication must be submitted to the Lodge which will then make appropriate adjustments and corrections having regard to the submission – Provincial Grand Lodge of Renfrewshire West.
All references in the Lodge Website and in these pages to “the Lodge” include references to all of the members of the Lodge and the Lodge Trustees and Office-bearers, all jointly and severally. The Provincial Grand Lodge of Renfrewshire West is a Provincial Grand Lodge of The Grand Lodge of Scotland and that Grand Lodge is the ultimate authority on all matters relating to Scottish Freemasonry.”
Privacy Policy
Privacy
The Provincial Grand Lodge of Renfrewshire West (herein after referred to as the ‘Lodge’) recognises the importance of protecting the privacy of the visitors to the Lodge Website. Any personal data collected through the Lodge Website will be regarded and treated as confidential and in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998. However, the collection of such data is unintentional as the Lodge has not designed or consciously put in place any system designed to collect personal information.
Disclaimer
The Lodge intends that the information published on the Lodge Website is up to date and accurate. However, the information on the Website does not constitute legal or professional advice, guidance or recommendation and the Lodge, its Office-bearers, Trustees and members, and each of them, will not accept any liability for actions arising from its use nor will they be held responsible for the contents of any Website or other source referenced by any external link.
Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that certain Websites write to a hard drive when a user visits that Website. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information a user personally supplies. A cookie cannot read data from a user’s hard disk or read cookie files created by other Websites. Cookies, however, enhance a Website’s performance in a number of ways including providing a secure way for to identity verification during a visit to a Website and personalising the user’s experience with the Lodge Website while making it more convenient for the user.
The Lodge may therefore use cookie technology to track or record information about visitors to the Lodge Website. These cookies are “session specific” and are not used to record personal information or to associate personal information with the use of the Lodge services.
Privacy and security are not compromised if and when the user accepts a cookie from the Lodge Website. Users can refuse cookies by turning them off on their web browsers (see under “Tools” and then “Internet Options”) and users do not need to have cookies turned on to successfully use the Website.
Questions or Suggestions
If ANYONE has any questions or suggestions regarding this policy or considers the Lodge is not properly adhering to it then the Lodge invites information and contents to be sent to the Lodge through the undernoted contact :- This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Hits: 616
Facebook
Twitter
Google+
Linkedin
